Expert: I think your friend has been a bit insensitive,
and she’s put you in a difficult position.
You have several different options.
You could say that you aren’t going if Angie goes,
but then you’ll put Susan in a difficult position.
Or you could just cancel, and suggest having another holiday later, with just the two of you.
Or you could invite someone else who you like, and then there would be four of you,
which is sometimes a better number than three.
But in fact, you don’t know Angie, and maybe you’ll like her.
So I think you should try to get to know her first.
If you like her, then the holiday will probably be a success.
If not, then you should tell your friend you aren’t going because you don’t think it will work with Angie.
You know, a bad holiday is worse than no holiday
Jane: Yes, that’s absolutely true. Thanks a lot.